[The Demon Hunter's Romance]
[Episode 7]
Good, you're here.
Where did you take my dad?
You've got some nerve.
I'm not afraid of you at all!
Is that so?
It's a trap again!
Impressive.
Take Tingzhou out.
No worries.
We're fully prepared.
There's no way he's getting away this time.
He's really here?
Let me see
who he is!
I'm here to help you!
[Heal and Help]
There's no big deal.
Take some medicine, and you'll be fine.
I'll prescribe it for you.
Thank you, Physician Jiu.
My Lady.
Actually, I heard you call me
last night.
But I don't know why.
I could hear,
but I just couldn't open my eyes
or move a bit.
You were bewitched by a demonic spell.
I seriously injured that demon.
It'll take him a while to recover.
Just in case,
the government should warn everyone in the city
not to play the game
of pear-genie summoning anymore.
Well...
If we issue such a notice as you said,
what are the people going to think
of our government office?
Then just buy
all the pears.
Well...
Wait, Xuanye...
Banxia,
come with me.
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
I'm fine.
You look like you're going to faint.
What are you going to do?
Xuanye...
Banxia,
come here.
Hey, you...
What's wrong with you?
Xuan...
What's this?
That Mirror Demon is still alive.
He might come again.
If you run into danger,
you must wake me up.
If you can't wake me,
just stab me with this.
Why should I stab you?
Did you
catch what I just said?
Yes.
But what's happening?
I'm feeling too drowsy.
I want to sleep.
What did the two of them go to do?
To sleep.
Sleep?
I don't think
this is appropriate.
Xuanye used the Mountain-shaking Sword.
Wait,
what does the Mountain-shaking Sword
have to do with sleeping?
Every sword he uses
takes a different toll on him.
Dubhe makes him gluttonous;
Mountain-shaking makes him sleepy.
But he still can't
drag My Lady into it.
This demon is hard to deal with.
Except Xuanye,
who else can protect
your lady?
Youhuang,
where are you going?
Youhuang!
I'm talking to you!
You ignore me every time I call you!
Youhuang!
Wait for me!
Um,
what should we do now?
What do you mean?
There's a demon around.
I'm too scared to go back home alone.
You can go find an inn.
Xuanye.
I'm so thirsty.
I want to have some water.
A cultivator? Seriously?
Don't you even know men and women should keep a proper distance?
I'm engaged, okay?
If they call off the engagement,
will you marry me instead?
Oh...
Jeez, seriously?
Well,
um...
And down here...
Sir,
what are you doing?
We didn't do anything illegal.
Why are you confiscating our pears?
Consider it as the government buying them from you.
You can go ask the government for money.
Well...
Sir,
I also have
some pears to sell at home.
Does the government need more?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Send them all to the government office
with none left!
Yes, sir. I'll fetch them right away.
Are you alright?
That demon hunter's power is overwhelming.
I'm no match for him.
We can't stay here any longer.
Go pack up.
We'll leave the city tonight.
You're so badly injured.
Where can we be
if not here?
You stay here for rehabilitation.
Let's make long-term plans
after you recover, okay?
How are things going out there?
Everything's fine.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I thought you wouldn't come tonight.
I was held up by the dance troupe.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
I'm willing to wait for my wife
no matter how long it takes.
Despite a few
twists and turns about our marriage,
my father
finally gave his consent to it.
He also said
he would give us a shop as a gift.
But the condition is that
we can neither invite our friends
nor hold a grand wedding at home.
I understand his concerns.
And I'm actually
quite tempted by that shop.
But after careful consideration,
I still said no.
Because I promised you
I will give you a proper and official wedding ceremony.
I also want everyone in the city
to know that
you will marry me,
and that you're the most beautiful woman in the world.
I don't want a grand wedding ceremony.
Let's leave this place together.
Let's go to a place
where no one knows us.
I have some savings.
I can keep you company when you study
and cook for you.
As long as I can be with you,
even if
it's just one year,
I'll have no regrets in my life.
You don't want to?
I do.
Having you is the best thing
I could ask for.
Who are you?
What do you want?
Don't you really want to
be with her?
Then I'll let you stay with her forever!
Li.
What are you busy with?
Nothing.
The mirror's face-down.
Why did you still come?
Didn't we agree that
when the mirror is flipped over,
that means I'm not available?
Is it necessary
between you and me?
Or
is there a secret
you don't want me to know?
Nope.
Just some women's issues.
What brings you here?
I'm here to send you a pear.
I've washed it.
Take it.
Didn't you promise me
you wouldn't kill people
for pears again before the right time?
That being said,
he made a wish.
I had to grant it.
I don't want to eat.
Li,
be good.
Don't infuriate me.
Good girl.
Why doesn't this pear have a fishy smell?
I almost forgot.
I couldn't help but kill him
as soon as he ate it.
I was supposed to wait seven days,
but I really couldn't help it.
When I saw his face,
I couldn't wait
to wipe him out immediately.
You mortals always say,
"What you eat makes who you are." Right?
The owner of this pear
is a scholar.
I guess
this pear
boasts some scholarly properties.
Eat it,
and you'll understand
the meaning of "loyalty"
and "fidelity."
Banxia.
You're awake.
Tingzhou and Chi Xue
went to buy groceries for me.
You must be hungry.
I've made some porridge.
Why did you leave?
Didn't I tell you
to stick around me?
But I didn't leave the Ganshan Clinic,
nor did I go out.
You slept for three whole days.
We've been tied together the whole time.
I needed to eat, drink,
wash up, and use the bathroom, right?
My bad. I forgot that.
I know you were worried about my safety.
But to protect me,
there's actually a simpler method.
What is it?
Draw another mark on me.
That monster hasn't been caught yet.
I'm afraid...
Done.
Xuanye.
I saw a scar on your chest.
When did you get that?
I saw it by accident.
It's a big scar.
Quite scary.
So when did you
get hurt?
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
That was a deep wound
so close to your heart.
You almost died.
How could you not remember?
I don't remember anything
from my childhood.
What are you looking at?
Do you want some more?
Xuanye,
can I
go get changed later?
It's been three days.
It's going to stink.
After I finish it
I'll escort you back.
Okay.
Chief.
Chief!
A weird case again!
What happened?
Another murder occurred.
The victim, Zhou Jingyuan,
24 years old,
a local in Guangping,
was found dead
this morning.
His case is quite similar to Tian Rui's.
But he didn't turn into a dried corpse
Didn't turn into a dried corpse?
He just aged a bit.
Are you Chief Constable Chu?
Yes, it's me.
Get up and talk.
Are you the one who reported the case?
Yes.
Sir,
I'm just a merchant.
I know little about
autopsies and how to crack cases.
But I've never seen anything
spookier than this
in my whole life.
May I see the body?
Please go ahead, sir.
My son...
My son!
How could you leave me,
your mother like this?
My son...
My son!
Son, what happened to you?
My son...
Auntie! Auntie!
Cuiying!
Auntie...
Hurry!
Go get a doctor!
Auntie...
Cuiying!
Come on, take her back to her room.
Cuiying...
Chief,
Zhou Jingyuan's room is right in the rear.
let's take a look.
♫Torturous lovesickness♫
♫Yet mutual confession is even harder♫
♫Drifting like a willow in the wind, yearning for a good ending♫
Jingyuan...
♫Side by side, we share a gaze too deep for words♫
It's my fault
♫Keep silent with no regrets♫
♫Share days and nights with you♫
♫In exchange for a lifelong deep love♫
♫Entwined through the endless night♫
♫Blossoms fell into eternal sleep in a blink♫
♫With no regrets, only joy in this life♫
♫Share days and nights with you♫
Because I promised you
I will give you a proper and official wedding ceremony.
♫In exchange for a lifelong deep love♫
I also want everyone in the city
to know that
you will marry me,
and that you're the most beautiful woman in the world.
♫Entwined through the endless night♫
♫Blossoms fell into eternal sleep in a blink♫
♫With no regrets, only joy in this life♫
What a coincidence.
My Lady.
My Lady?
Why did you call me so loudly? Almost startled me.
I've already been here for a while.
What kept you so lost in thought,
My Lady?
Nothing.
Do your work now.
You're done?
I've thought it through.
Before we catch the Mirror Demon,
you have to stay with me.
Okay.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
[Ganshan Clinic]
Ms. Ji Li?
Hello, Miss Duan.
What a coincidence.
What brings you here?
Our dance troupe's invaded by rats.
I came to buy a rat killer.
You even sell that?
Miss Duan,
I have something to attend to. So I'll take my leave.
Chi Xue.
What did that woman just buy?
Rat killer.
Anything else?
And a bottle of insect oil.
What's insect oil?
You have something to do with it?
Another person died on North Street this morning.
The victim was
a young scholar.
After his sudden death,
he turned into a middle-aged man.
That woman you saw just now
was there mourning the deceased.
I guess they knew each other.
But I can't help feeling that
this whole thing is kind of fishy.
Insect oil is used to ward off evil things.
When applied to a sharp weapon,
it can cause damage to a demon's spiritual body.
If it hits a vital spot,
it can certainly be fatal.
Now it all makes sense.
That woman
must know the whereabouts of the demon.
Where is she?
She once said
they were from the Yunmen Dance Troupe.
Yunmen Dance Troupe?
The one who died at Yanlai Restaurant last time,
the dancer named Tian Rui,
was also one of the Yunmen Dance Troupe.
Let's go find her.
Didn't the previous victims
all age abnormally when they died?
Why did the victim
turn middle-aged this time?
Didn't Physician Jiu mention that
it'd take seven full days
for a jade pear
to fully absorb the life force
of the host eating the pear?
I guess this time, that demon took out the pear
before the time was up.
Am I right, Physician Jiu?
Maybe.
Then why would he do this?
Guess he messed up the timing.
Messed up the timing
of things like this? Really?
Well, demons
are all about murdering humans
and are quite dumb.
What's so surprising about that?
Could that be the truth?
Or maybe he just couldn't wait
to kill that man on the spot.
Chief Constable Chu.
Banxia?
What brings you here?
We're here to find Ms. Ji Li.
She's left.
What? Where did she go?
She bid farewell to the Manager yesterday,
saying she'd be heading south.
And she's already left the Dance Troupe.
How long has it been
since we last sat down
and had a proper meal together like this?
Whenever you visited,
you made me eat those jade pears
with a fishy smell
and an awful taste.
As time went by,
I'd recall that fishiness
at the sight of you every time.
That's why I keep quarreling with you.
Thinking about it now,
I really shouldn't have acted this way.
Today on the street,
I ran into a woman in her sixties,
gray-haired
and wrinkled.
Just one look
and it was terrifying.
A woman's youth
is rather fleeting.
Only about one or two decades.
Just like a flower,
before you can even appreciate it,
it withers.
What a pity.
But luckily,
I have you.
You love me, spoil me,
and make jade pears for me,
helping me stay young for 20 years.
This is something
countless people dream of.
Yet I was ungrateful,
quarreling with you,
saying things that hurt you,
and doing things you hated.
Thinking about it now,
I was really rebellious.
I never blame you.
Really?
Really.
Chuan,
thank you.
Li,
don't cry.
Let bygones
be bygones.
As long as we can
stay together forever,
nothing else matters.
I've made up my mind.
When we leave this place
and reach Jiangnan,
let's find a nice place with mountains
and water.
I don't want to be in the public eye anymore.
I just want to be with you,
do the washing and cooking,
play music and dance,
and never see anyone else again.
How does that sound?
I've been looking forward to that kind of life
for years.
I've also been looking forward to that kind of life
for a long time.
Do you have to do this?
How many times has this happened?
Do you really want me dead?
I've been so good to you,
yet you betrayed me
and had an affair with someone else.
I don't even blame you!
You've really disappointed me.
Sirs and madam, are you here to book some rooms?
We're here on official business.
Yes, sir.
Have you seen a girl
around 17 or 18,
slender in build,
with deep-set eyes?
She should have come alone.
No.
Please try to recall again.
She's very fair-skinned, thin,
and pretty.
It really doesn't ring a bell.
Sir,
I think I've seen
the person you described.
Where is she?
Upstairs, in the second room from the left.
That girl looks
like she stepped out of a painting.
Her waist is very slim.
I heard from some other guests that
he's a dancer from Yunmen Dance Troupe.
What kind of place is this?
Are you playing tricks again?
Yeah,
I forgot that
you don't remember anything.
Let me help you recall it.
Back then,
you were sold to the mansion as a dancer.
At first, you led
a pretty good life.
But as time went by,
you grew older,
losing your youthful charm
and favor.
Even the servants in the mansion
could bully you at will
and treat you like a toy.
You were resentful.
Day and night, you made wishes in front of the mirror,
hoping to regain your youth.
I
heard your voice
and came to you
to fulfill your wish.
Not only did you regain your beauty,
but I also helped you take revenge
by killing those who once hurt you.
You're talking nonsense!
I'm talking nonsense?
Mirrors
actually reflect
human hearts.
Greed
comes at a price.
Look at your face.
So young,
so radiant.
How gorgeous.
It's taken numerous human lives
to maintain such a beautiful face.
Over these years,
how many people have you killed?
That bookworm,
if he knew that
your beauty
is backed by so much bloodshed,
would he still love you?
Would he?
Would he really?
I didn't do that!
You didn't?
What do you mean?
Didn't kill with your own hands?
Or didn't harm any lives?
Don't tell me
you have no idea how this pear
is made.
Li,
come on...
That's too hypocritical.
I tried to kill myself.
I once tried to kill myself.
Right!
I attempted that!
You didn't allow it.
You stopped me!
If you really wanted to die,
could I have kept an eye on you day and night?
The path
is yours to walk on your own.
Is it so hard to admit that
you're a cruel,
cold-blooded creature?
You're truly a devil.
It was you.
You deceived me.
You beguiled me into eating the pears,
saying they'd keep me young
and alive forever!
You deceived me,
turning me into
a monster like you!
Li,
people
can't have everything they ask for.
I just want to leave you.
What did you say?
I don't know why
I met you.
You must have bewitched me.
I never want to eat those
stinking, fishy pears again.
I only want to stay with the person
I love!
Dream on!
Having drained people's blood
and reaped all the benefits,
you still dream about
living a normal life?
I'd rather die
than live with you.
They called you a flirt,
obsessed with seducing men,
born with no shame.
I don't believe it.
I don't!
I love you deeply.
Have you forgotten that?
You're a demon!
You're not human.
Do you know what love is?
Do you understand it at all?
Every moment
with you,
I hate myself.
This isn't love at all.
You don't deserve to talk about love!
I don't deserve that?
You're my one and only love
in my whole life!
What? I don't deserve it?
Do you think you deserve it?
No!
I've destroyed myself with my own hands.
I hate you.
And I hate myself even more.
They were right.
I am a flirt
obsessed with seducing men,
born with no shame.
I can be
with anyone.
Literally anyone!
Except you.
I'd rather age and die
than be with you!
Don't talk like that!
I knew it.
You think
after all these years,
this is really the first time
you've fallen in love with someone?
You think we've only been together
for twenty years?
What do you mean by that?
It'll be okay.
Don't be afraid.
After today,
we can be back to how we used to be.
Don't touch me!